Eric Lake

Front End Web Developer

Englewood, CO (303)548-9271 ericlake@me.com

https://github.com/yohuck | https://www.linkedin.com/in/eric-lake/ | https://yohuck.github.io/eric-lake-portfolio/

Front end web developer with background in Customer Operations focused on building inviting, accessible, responsive front-end user interfaces. Experience building processes from startup through acquisition and a strong understanding of customer perspective.

Technical skills:

Svelte, React, JavaScript ES6+, CSS3, HTML5, GitHub, Node.js, jQuery, Bootstrap, Bulma, D3

PROJECTS

Habit Stack | https://habitstack.herokuapp.com/ | https://github.com/yohuck/habit-map

- SUMMARY: Full stack habit tracking application with custom CSS data visualization
- ROLE: Lead developer
- TOOLS: JavaScript, Node.js, Handlebars, Sequelize, MySql, Express, CSS

Recycle Better | https://yohuck.github.io/wish-cycle/ | https://github.com/yohuck/wish-cycle

- SUMMARY: Application to help make informed recycling/disposal decisions and to find nearby specialty recycling centers.
- ROLE: Lead developer
- TOOLS: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, API, Bulma

City Weather | https://yohuck.github.io/city-weather/ | https://github.com/yohuck/city-weather

- SUMMARY: Weather application that provides current & forecasted weather data by city and saves recent searches.
- ROLE: Sole author
- TOOLS: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, API

Schedule Simple | https://yohuck.github.io/schedule-simple | https://github.com/yohuck/schedule-simple

- SUMMARY: Weather application that provides current & forecasted weather data by city and saves recent searches.
- ROLE: Sole author
- TOOLS: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, API

CodePen Gallery | https://yohuck.github.io/characters/| https://github.com/yohuck/characters

• SUMMARY: Clickable CSS art, animations, and custom buttons.

EXPERIENCE

Stack Sports | CaptainU

Senior Customer Success Manager | CaptainU | Denver, CO

JAN 2020 - PRESENT

- Increased LTV 30% by designing and implementing customer onboarding and engagement process for 5M annual revenue customer base.
- Assisted product manager by creating impact analysis reports, compiling customer feedback, and writing user stories.
- Boosted social engagement over 100% with 50,000+ minutes viewed across social channels by writing, producing, and hosting bi-weekly customer educational social content as well as paywalled content for subscribers and expert content for key partners.
- Managed all customer success processes for 5M annual revenue customer base.

Customer Service Manager for Athlete & Team Solutions | Stack Sports | Denver, CO DEC 2018 - JAN 2020

- Maintained 90% CSAT across 5 newly acquired SAAS products with teams across 3 continents
- Merged, managed, and standardized processes, tools, reporting, and training for customer service teams across all athlete & team products.
- Collaborated with VP of Ops and product managers to plan and implement customer strategy.

Customer Service Manager | CaptainU | Denver, CO

JAN 2015 - DEC 2018

- Built the customer service team for quickly growing startup product from scratch.
- Created all customer service hiring, onboarding, and internal educational materials.
- Implemented KPI tracking and customer feedback reporting process for product manager.

Customer Service Agent | CaptainU | Denver, CO

FEB 2013 - JAN 2015

- Hired as employee twelve as the first customer service agent for college sports SAAS startup.
- Answered and documented all customer inquiries
- Built initial knowledge base and implemented CRM to increase efficiency and improve reporting.

Customer Service Representative | SharedInk | Portland, OR

APR 2011 - FEB 2013

- Managed customer orders from receipt to fulfillment for digital printed photo book projects.
- Answered all customer support inquired
- Managed social media pages

EDUCATION

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development

University of Denver - 2022